[rock guitar riff playing]
‎好了 我用时多少？
Done. What was my time?
‎快得很
It was very fast.
‎好吧
All right.
‎该给前门的合页上油了吧？
It's time to oil
the hinges on the front door, huh?
‎-给我计时
‎-预备…开始！
-Time me.
-And… go!
‎嗯 我连…连秒表都不带用的
Yeah, I'm not…
I'm not even using the stopwatch.
‎出了那点小意外之后
‎他活动起来还挺灵活的
He's moving around pretty good
after his little accident.
‎你是说你骑车撞了他之后？
Oh, you mean
when you ran over him with your bike?
‎能不能别哪壶不开提哪壶？
Gosh, are you ever gonna
let me live that down?
‎两天过去了
‎他腰上的车胎印还没消呢
It was two days ago.
He still has a tire track on his hip.
[thunderclap]
‎哇 这雨下得 简直六亲不认
Wow, it is rainin'
tits and livers out there.
‎这雨肯定下起来没完
This rain is never gonna let up.
‎我本该把家里的旧东西都捐了
‎现在干不成了
I was supposed to donate
all our old junk today, but now I can't.
‎即便东西是湿的 教会也不介意
Oh, the church won't mind
if your stuff is wet.
‎我捐了一箱沾满焦糖的旧胸罩
I gave 'em a box of old bras
that were covered in caramel,
‎他们可高兴了
and they were thrilled.
‎不是 这一下雨 雷德就不会出门
Yeah, no. Now that it's raining,
Red won't leave the house,
‎他什么都不让我扔
and he never lets me get rid of anything.
‎1975年花四块钱买个开罐器
‎他也要带进棺材里陪葬
If he paid four dollars
for a can opener in 1975,
‎1975年花四块钱买个开罐器
‎他也要带进棺材里陪葬
he wants to be buried with it.
‎我有个舅舅
‎入土时还戴着“绿湾包装工队”的头盔
I had a uncle that was buried
in a Packers helmet,
‎但那是因为我们摘不下来
but that was just because
we couldn't get it off.
‎-听见前门开了吗？
‎-没有
-Did you hear the front door open?
-No.
‎这就对了
Exactly.
‎因为咱家的合页
‎绝对是本街区最安静的
Because we have
the quietest hinges on the block.
‎科瓦尔斯基家算老几！
And the Kowalskis can suck it!
‎好了…还有啥东西坏了？
So… what else is on the fritz?
‎雷德 来我家帮帮忙吧
Red, you should come help me.
‎孩子们夏天一直宅在家
‎都快把房子拆了
The kids have been home all summer
trashin' my house.
‎一连几个钟头 你都不愁没活儿干
I could keep you busy for hours.
‎好主意
Oh, that is a great idea.
‎没错 那天掉了一个门把手
Yeah. The other day,
a doorknob fell off in my hand,
‎现在 那屋我们都不进了
and now that's just
a room we don't go in anymore.
‎坏了 屋里还有条鱼
Oh shoot.
We had a fish in there.
‎雷德 你就爱往下水道冲死鱼
Red, you love to flush a dead fish.
‎那他得先修好厕所
‎冲水的时候会发出这样的声音
But he's gonna
have to fix the toilet first.
‎那他得先修好厕所
‎冲水的时候会发出这样的声音
It makes a sound like this when you flush.
[makes bubbling noise]
[makes squealing sound]
‎赶紧带路
Take me there!
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎抱歉让你们看到
‎杰伊留下这么恶心的吻痕
I'm sorry you have to see
this disgusting hickey I got from Jay.
‎我…觉得好难为情
I… I'm so embarrassed.
‎莉亚 明明啥都没有啊
Leia, there's literally nothing there.
‎不 靠近一点 可恶心了
No, no, no. Get up close.
It's… It's so gross.
‎她想载歌载舞 我们偏偏不买账
She wants a big song and dance,
but we are not giving it to her.
‎我还在适应你和杰伊的关系
I'm still getting used to
you and Jay being an official thing.
‎就像我发现狗有月经时一样
It's like when I found out
that dogs got periods.
‎我心想：“啊？”
And I was like, "Huh?"
‎既然你在惦记吻痕
The fact that you even think
you have a hickey
‎就说明杰伊的嘴亲上了你的脖子
means that Jay's mouth was on your neck.
‎-所以有事发生咯？
‎-确实有事发生
-So stuff's happening?
-Stuff's happening.
‎昨晚 我们盖着毯子
I got this big guy last night
‎在豆子袋上面抱抱
‎然后我就有了这一大块吻痕
while we were cuddled up on a beanbag
under a blanket.
‎这样啊
Oh, I see.
‎-那你摸了吗？
‎-摸了什么？
-So did you touch it?
-Touch what?
‎摸过你就不会问了
You don't ask that if you touched it.
‎那个呀？
Oh, it? [chuckles]
‎-你为什么这么说？
‎-我不知道
-Why would you even say that?
-I don't know.
‎毯子加上豆子袋通常等于摸那玩意儿
Blanket plus bean bag
usually equals touching it.
‎这么简单的性学算数
It's simple sex math.
‎我不知道“那个”还有别的意思
I didn't know, um,
things mean other things.
‎莉亚 所有东西都有所指
Everything means something, Leia.
‎别跟她说这个
Don't start this with her.
‎莉亚 这种事没有规矩
‎别让他们扰乱你的思维
Leia, there are no rules to any of this.
Don't let them get in your head.
‎谢谢 格温
Thank you, Gwen.
‎我要说清楚 我不会碰的
‎你们觉得他会觉得我会摸吗？
Just to be clear, I'm not gonna touch it.
‎我要说清楚 我不会碰的
‎你们觉得他会觉得我会摸吗？
‎摸什么？
-D'you think he thinks I'm gonna touch it?
-Touch what?
‎我们梦想的…天空
The sky! [chuckles] With our… dreams.
‎就是因为这样 我才讨厌下雨
This is why I hate rain.
[grunting]
‎合上就行了
Just close it.
Oh.
[chuckles]
‎好主意 宝贝
Good call, babe.
‎一 二 三 四
-[rock music playing]
-One, two, three, four!
‎在街上闲逛
♪ Hangin' out down the street ♪
‎和上周没什么两样
♪ The same old thing we did last week ♪
‎没什么事好做 就跟你唠唠嗑
♪ Not a thing to do ♪
♪ But talk to you ♪
‎这样挺好 这样挺好
♪ We're all all right! ♪
‎（90年代秀）
‎你好 威斯康辛！
[young woman] Hello, Wisconsin!
‎你这么一说
‎我总在想和杰伊做的所有事
Now you've got me thinking about
everything I've done with Jay.
‎比如 那晚我们一起吃了个布丁杯
‎这是什么意思？
Like, the other night, we shared
a pudding cup. What does that mean?
‎-等等 一个勺子还是两个？
‎-一个
-Wait, one spoon or two?
-One.
‎你可能怀孕了
You might be pregnant.
‎谁想来点高级糖果？
Ah. Who wants to try some fancy candy?
‎我爸从日本寄了一整箱炫酷的东西
My dad sent me
a whole box of cool stuff from Japan.
‎他在那边打棒球 有点厉害
He plays baseball over there.
Kind of a big deal.
‎他是联盟里最老的球员
He's the oldest player in the league.
‎还给日本成人纸尿裤做广告
He does adult diaper commercials
over there.
‎这样怎么就不酷了
I don't get why that's not cool.
‎别管我 孩子们
‎我去后面拿一些雷德的破烂儿
Don't mind me, kids.
‎别管我 孩子们
‎我去后面拿一些雷德的破烂儿
I'm just gonna grab
some of Red's junk from the back.
‎就当我没来过
I was never here.
‎我们的货还藏在那儿呢
That's where we keep the stash.
‎没事儿 上回我把它藏在这里了
It's cool. Last time I hid it in this.
‎（狗狗零食）
‎没有人会找到这里来
‎因为他们已经不养狗了
No one's gonna look in here
'cause they don't have a dog anymore.
‎这个得丢掉 我们已经不养狗了
Oh, oh. This has to go.
We don't have a dog anymore.
‎奶奶把藏货拿走了！
Granny has the stash!
‎-你为什么要给她？
‎-我能怎么办 格温？
-Why did you just give it to her?
-What was I supposed to do, Gwen?
‎不给她！
Not give it to her!
‎等一下
Hang on, hang on.
‎兄弟 我一向挺你的
I've always got your back, bro.
‎但这回不行 你也太衰了
But not now. That was terrible.
‎听着 这不是问题
Look, it's not a problem.
‎我去拿回来就是了
I'll just go get it.
‎福尔曼太太
‎你家一模一样的箱子可真多
Mrs. Forman, you have
a lot of identical boxes.
‎这才几个呀 你应该去车库看看
Oh, this isn't even the half of it.
You should see the garage.
[laughs]
[forced laughter]
‎出大事了
We have a big problem.
‎所以需要一个解决大方案
Which requires a big solution.
‎你们谁有主意吗？
Does anybody have one?
‎我们得分头去找
We need to split up and look for it.
‎妮基和我上楼找
Nikki and I will take upstairs.
[clicks tongue]
‎不行 你们俩一旦独处
‎肯定会找个阴暗的犄角旮旯
No, if you two are alone,
you're just gonna find some dark corner
‎相互乱摸
to hump all over each other.
‎好吧 杰伊跟我一起
Fine, Jay and I can go together.
‎你们两个凑在一起 就只知道聊
If you guys are together,
you'll just talk about
‎最爱尚格云顿电影里哪段性爱场景
your favorite sex scenes
in Jean-Claude Van Damme movies.
‎-《铁拳无敌》
‎-《拳霸天下》
-Lionheart.
-Bloodsport.
‎-《终极标靶》！
[both] Hard Target!
‎内特和我上楼找
Nate and I will go upstairs.
‎奥兹和杰伊去车库翻箱子
Ozzie, you and Jay
go through the boxes in the garage.
‎-莉亚和我在这里找
‎-但我们知道不在这里
-Yeah, Leia and I will look down here.
-But we know it's not down here.
‎那就搞定了呗
Then I guess we're done.
‎别担心 莉亚 我最合适干这个了
Don't worry, Leia.
I'm the right man for this job.
[door opens, closes]
‎搞什么啊？
What the hell was that?
‎干嘛？我亲吻男友嘛
What? I kissed my boyfriend.
‎不是 你的胳膊是在干嘛？
No. What were you doing with your arms?
‎在你身后支楞着 跟玩跳台滑雪似的
They were sticking out behind you
like a ski jumper.
‎都怪你把我弄糊涂了 现在
‎我不知道干啥有啥意义…该摸他哪里
You got in my head, and now I don't know
what means what or… where to touch him.
‎随便吧 我们现在
‎有更重要的事要操心
Whatever. We have way bigger things
to worry about now.
‎好像不是呢
I don't think we do!
[rock music playing]
‎你知道我们该怎么做吗？
Do you know what we should do?
‎我们应该去找警察
‎借条缉毒的警犬过来
We should go to the cops and ask to borrow
one of those drug-sniffing dogs.
‎我跟你怎么会沾亲？
How are we even related?
‎咱俩是一个妈生的
We have the same mom. [snickers]
‎你为什么总这么问我？
Why do you always ask me that?
Aww!
‎你们上来帮我啦
You kids came up here to help me.
‎好贴心
You are so sweet.
‎还有你 我正用得上你的大块头
And you, I really need
your muscles right now.
‎福尔曼太太 我…
[chuckles] Mrs. Forman, I…
‎我有女朋友了
I have a girlfriend.
‎拜托
Oh please.
[laughs]
‎这身肉给了你都不知道从哪下手
You wouldn't know what to do with this.
‎雷德在楼上放了一个巨大的木雕驼鹿
No. Red has a giant wooden moose
in the upstairs closet.
‎多年来 我一直想把它扔了
And I've been trying
to get rid of it for years,
‎但太沉了 我搬不动
but it's too heavy for me to lift.
‎没问题 有男人帮忙 就不用问我了
Oh sure. Don't ask me
because you need a man to help.
‎冷静 埃莉诺罗斯福
Oh, calm down, Eleanor Roosevelt.
‎我只想把那个蠢东西弄走
I just want the stupid thing
out of the house.
‎好吧
Okay.
‎你去搬驼鹿 我继续在这里帮忙
Go get the moose,
and I'll keep helping down here.
‎交给我
On it.
‎你能描述一下这只木头驼鹿吗？
Can you describe this wooden moose to me?
‎就是只驼鹿
It's a moose.
‎不过是木头做的
But made of wood.
‎我会尽力的
I'll do my best.
‎太糟糕了
This sucks.
‎昨天我吻杰伊的时候还很自在
Yesterday I was totally comfortable
kissing Jay.
‎你现在就像一个不想被人抱的娃娃
[chuckles] Now you look like a baby
that doesn't want to get picked up.
‎我知道我干了啥！
I know what I did!
‎对不起 我有点过意不去
Oh, I'm sorry. I feel bad.
‎我只是想给你建议 不是让你伤脑筋
I was trying to give you advice,
not break your brain.
‎我需要建议
I need advice.
‎杰伊有很多经验
Jay has a lot of experience.
‎我最接近嘿咻的一次
The closest I've come to having sex
‎是在划水槽上 裤头卡了屁股
is when I got a front wedgie
on a Slip 'N Slide.
‎嗯 头得先进去
Yeah. You gotta go headfirst.
‎我就是那样做的
I did.
‎我朋友的妈妈是机械工程师
My friend's mom is a mechanical engineer.
‎她都懵了
She was baffled.
‎听着 别想太多
Look, don't overthink it.
‎顺其自然吧 只是别碰他的头发
Just do what comes naturally.
Except don't touch his hair.
‎我一碰内特的头发
‎就触发了裤头里的开关
If I go near Nate's hair,
it flips a switch in his pants.
‎还有开关？
There's a switch?
‎男孩子真是太复杂了
These boys are so complicated!
‎才没有呢
They're really not.
‎把手放在他屁股上
Just put your hands on his hips.
‎距离够近 他知道你感兴趣
It's close enough to the good stuff
so he knows that you're interested,
‎但又保持距离 让他明白你没有出手
but far enough away
so he knows you're not making a move.
‎明白了
Got it.
‎亲亲往后摸 拉链管拉锁
Lips are for hips
like zippers are for zips.
‎我是这么记州府的
It's how I learned my state capitals.
‎别再这样了
Never do that again.
‎-中大奖了
‎-你找到了？
-Jackpot.
-You found it?
‎没有 我找到了一整箱万圣节旧服装
No, I found a whole box
of old Halloween costumes.
‎应该是只蜜蜂
I think this is supposed to be a bee.
‎可怜的福尔曼太太 你尽力了
Oh, Mrs. Forman, bless your heart.
You tried.
‎奥兹 别闹了 我们不是在扮家家
Ozzie, stop messing around.
We're not playing dress-up.
‎那就把你找到那件旧外套脱了
Then take off that old jacket you found.
‎拜托 我穿着超像克里斯蒂安史莱特
Come on. Makes me look
like Christian Slater.
‎咱俩想的肯定
‎不是同一个克里斯蒂安史莱特
We must be thinking of
different Christian Slaters.
‎快看！
[Ozzie] Oh look!
‎好得很 找到了
Oh! Sweet. You found it.
‎你今天经历了精彩冒险呢
‎小包包 我们回家吧
You have had quite the adventure today,
little baggie. Let's get you home.
‎你们在我家车库做什么？
-What are you doing in my garage?
-Uh…
‎我们在等你
We were… waiting for you.
‎你迟到了
You're late.
‎福尔曼先生 说说你今天过得怎么样
Tell us about your day, Mr. Forman.
‎好了 现在你们该走了
All right, this is when you leave.
‎把外套还我
And give me that jacket.
‎这可是我1964年
‎在西尔斯百货花全价买的
I paid full price for that thing
at Sears in 1964.
‎滚出我的车库
Get out of my garage.
‎你们属于地下室！
You're basement people!
[rock music playing]
[Nate strains]
‎-是这个吗？
‎-不 是另一个
-Is this it?
-No, it's the other one.
‎我搞错了
Oh, my bad.
‎没有 我开玩笑的
No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
[laughs]
‎他开玩笑没用的
You can't do that with him.
‎-好大
‎-好重
-That is big.
-And heavy.
‎还蠢到家
And stupid.
‎（阪神虎）
‎等等…那是我爸爸寄给我的衬衫
Wait… That's the shirt my dad sent me.
‎你把它弄得脏兮兮 还给剪了
You got stuff all over it and cut it up.
‎反正对你来说也太小了
‎就像咱家的淋浴一样
It's too small for you, anyway.
Just like our shower.
‎我听见你在浴室里叮铃咣啷
‎就像只掉进垃圾箱的狗熊
I hear you banging around in there
like a bear that fell in a dumpster.
‎我那叫动感淋浴
I take an athletic shower.
‎别试图转换话题
‎你不能随便碰我的东西
And don't try to change the subject.
You can't just touch my stuff.
‎你是说像这样？这样？这样？
You mean like this? And this? And this?
‎-别闹了 格温！
‎-好了 我明白你们为什么吵架
-Quit it, Gwen!
-Okay, I understand why you're fighting.
‎都是他害的
He… He does this to people.
‎我们把他弄出去吧
Let's just get him out!
Get him out!
‎-你会付出代价的
‎-你是在犯傻
-You're gonna pay.
-You're being an idiot.
‎你的脸才犯傻
Your face is being an idiot.
‎-这话驴唇不对马嘴
‎-是啊 不对
-That doesn't even make sense.
-Yeah. It doesn't.
[imitates explosion]
[rock music playing]
‎藏货…在雷德手上
Red… has the stash.
‎哦 好吧 稍等哈
Cool, cool. Yeah. Um, hang on one second.
[muffled scream]
‎那我们现在怎么办？
So what do we do now?
‎没关系
It's okay.
‎他自己还不知道
He doesn't even know he has it yet.
‎对吧 奥兹？
Right, Ozzie?
‎知道什么？
Has what?
‎我只是一个纯真无辜的小孩子
‎倒霉碰上一群小混混
I'm just a sweet innocent kid who got
caught up with some no-good riffraff.
‎你这个只顾自保的混蛋
You save-yourself son of a bitch.
‎我敬重你
I respect that.
‎-好了 赶紧去拿吧
‎-这就去
-Now, go get it.
-We will.
‎我只是…想跟莉亚道别
‎以防再也见不到她了
I just… wanted to come say goodbye to Leia
in case I never saw her again.
Aww. [laughs softly]
‎你还去不去了？
Are we doing this?
Uh…
[Leia] Mm-hmm…
‎莉亚…把手挪开呗
Leia… move your hands.
‎我们又回到老地方了
And we're back to that.
‎嗨 雪莉 听着 我还需要一些时间
Hi, Sherri. Listen.
I'm gonna need more time.
‎我不知道还能拖多久
‎能干的全被他干完了
I don't know how much more I can stall.
He's done everything.
‎我觉得我家的合页比你家的还安静
I think my hinges are quieter than yours.
‎这个嘛…我看未必
Well… I doubt that.
[laughs]
‎你就…瞎编点由头 再见
Just… Just make something up. Bye.
[screaming]
‎怎么了？
What?
‎我好像看到一只老鼠
‎很大 看起来就像半只耗子！
I think I just saw a mouse.
It was big. It looked half-rat!
‎它马上就要一命呜呼了
Well, it's about to be all dead.
[rock music playing]
‎坚强大男孩在这里呢
Well, there's my big, strong boy.
‎还是那句话…我有主儿了哈
Again… I'm spoken for.
Oh.
‎真可惜
What a shame.
‎-看看我从你的枕头底下拿了什么
‎-你拿这个做什么？
-Look what I took from under your pillow.
-What are you doing with that?
‎她看起来挺横 但没有弗兰基毯毯
She looks all tough,
but she can't fall asleep
‎她就睡不着
without Frankie the Blankie.
‎他也需要我
He needs me too.
‎你动我的东西 我就用弗兰基蹭屁股
You touch my stuff,
Frankie gets butt-flossed.
‎-弗兰基！
‎-喂
-Frankie!
-Hey.
[Gwen grunting]
‎-滚开！
‎-不！
-Get off!
-No!
[Nate grunting]
‎好吧 那我去洗手间
Fine. Then I'm going to the bathroom.
‎-我恨你！
-Eww! I hate you!
-I hate you!
‎我恨你
I hate you!
[rock music playing]
‎在这里呢 我们拿上赶紧走吧
There it is.
Let's grab it and get out of here.
‎等等！这也太容易了
‎如果是陷阱呢？
Wait! This feels too easy.
What if it's a trap?
‎你看太多动画…
You've seen too many car--
‎-还真是陷阱！
‎-我就知道！
-[sharp snap]
-It's a trap!
‎-还真是陷阱！
‎-我就知道！
I knew it! [screams]
[trap snaps]
[groans in pain]
‎别动
Freeze!
[trap snaps]
‎该死
-Damn it!
-[trap snaps]
Ow!
‎这里简直是地狱！
This place is hell!
‎这几乎和划水槽事件如出一辙
This is almost as bad as
the Slip 'N Slide incident.
‎我家邻居康妮还得手把手…教我弄开
My neighbor Connie had to coach me through
getting it out.
‎哇 我家邻居连招呼都不打
Wow. My neighbors don't even wave hello.
‎我讨厌这种怪怪的感觉
I hate how weird everything is.
‎我希望能快进到你和内特的状态
I wish I could just fast-forward
to where you and Nate are.
‎一切都很轻松
Where, like, things are easy. [scoffs]
‎相信我 并不总是那么轻松
Believe me, it's not always easy.
‎内特和我对未来的看法很不一样
Nate and I aren't really
on the same page about our futures.
‎最近 我们总为各种事情瞎吵
Now, we're having
the dumbest fights about everything.
‎比如遇上龙卷风怎么办
Like what to do if there's a tornado.
‎我说躲进地下室
I say hide in a basement.
‎他想当乘风少年
He wants to ride one.
‎我只想说 事情永远不会完美
I'm just saying,
things are never going to be perfect.
‎至于你跟杰伊那件事 确实很糟糕
And as for what happened with Jay,
sure, it was bad.
‎但总不会比告诉大家更糟糕
But it's not gonna be
as bad as when we tell everyone.
‎谢谢
Thanks.
‎-我们拿到了
‎-是吗？
-We got it.
-You did?
‎可能让我失去了一根脚趾
Might have cost me a toe.
‎我不敢看 但我感觉袜子湿了
I'm afraid to look, but my sock feels wet.
‎嘿 刚才的事
Hey, so, about earlier.
‎什么？我都不知道你在说什么
What? I don't even know
what you're talking about.
‎他刚才一直念叨呢
Uh, that's all he talked about.
‎我只是想太多
‎担心会把我们的关系搞得很怪
I just got in my head about us,
and I'm worried I made things weird.
‎我们能不能忘掉之前
‎回到过去的样子？
Can we just forget about it
and go back to the way it was?
‎比如你给我这一大块吻痕的时候？
Like when you gave me this huge hickey?
‎-在哪儿来着？
‎-重点是…
-Where is it again?
-The point is…
‎我希望我们之间可以开心舒服
I just want things to be
fun and comfortable again.
‎那…你想要的就是我想要的
Well… I want what you want.
‎很好 因我想要这个
Good, because this is what I want.
‎你的脚趾好恶心！
Ew, your toe!
‎我想看看
Ooh, I wanna see.
‎你亲了我的耳朵
You kissed my ear.
‎那你别转头啊！
Stop turning!
[rock music playing]
‎别冲我喘气
Stop breathing on me.
‎好了 够了
-[loud, hissing exhale]
-Okay, that's enough.
‎你俩怎么回事？赶紧的 动手
What's your problem? Come on. Chop-chop.
‎好吧
Fine.
‎它不是普通的衬衫 是我爸送的
[scoffs] That wasn't just any shirt.
It's from my dad.
‎-但你穿根本不合身
‎-这不重要
-But it didn't even fit you.
-It doesn't matter.
‎他亲自买了放进箱子里
He went out and bought it
and… and put it in the box.
‎是他亲自动手的
His hands were on it. [sighs]
‎你不会明白的
‎你比我更常见到自己的爸爸
You wouldn't understand.
You see your dad way more than I do.
‎没错 但我还是很想他
Yeah, but I still miss him.
‎我只有在他经过这里
‎去另一个城市时才能见到他
I only ever get to see him when he comes
through town on his way to another city.
‎马戏团演员？
Circus performer?
‎这是开的哪路脑洞？
How is that your first guess?
‎他是卡车司机
He's a truck driver.
‎不过 如果我知道你的感受
‎我就绝不会动它
But, Nate, if I'd known how you felt,
I never would have touched it.
‎也不会剪
Or cut it up.
‎或者让车子碾过做旧
Or let cars run over it
to make it look vintage.
‎没关系 反正很傻
It's fine. It's dumb.
‎不 一点都不傻
No, it's not dumb.
‎这对我们俩来说都很糟糕
It sucks for both of us.
‎大笨蛋 你把我弄哭了
You idiot. You made me cry.
‎-我恨你
‎-我也恨你
-I hate you.
-I hate you too.
‎我也想爸爸
I miss my dad too.
‎在我十岁生日的时候
‎他带我去看赛狗
He took me to the dog track
on my tenth birthday.
‎还让我抿了一口他的啤酒
And he gave me a sip of his beer,
‎我把爆米花吐出来了
‎而且还是爆米花的形状
and I barfed up my popcorn,
‎我把爆米花吐出来了
‎而且还是爆米花的形状
and it still looked like popcorn.
‎雷德回来了！他就在我后面！
Red's coming! He's right behind me!
‎他拄着拐棍儿 我们可能还有时间
He's got that cane,
so maybe we've got some time.
‎内特 马上把驼鹿弄走
Nate, moose, now.
‎我来帮你
Let me help you.
‎-谢了 老妹
‎-有我呢 老哥
-Thanks, sis. [chuckles]
-I got you, big bro.
‎我家孩子怎么这么懂事？
‎他们偷喝你家酒了？
Why are my kids being nice?
Did they get into your wine?
‎没有 我们…就是小感动了一下
No. We… We had an emotional moment.
‎他们都很想念爸爸
They both were missing their dads.
Oh.
‎哎 听这话 我就像挨了窝心脚
Man, that's always a gut punch.
‎不 这又不是世界末日
No. It wasn't the end of the world.
‎内特的爸爸
‎给他寄了一件T恤衫 但是太小了
No, no. Nate's father sent him a T-shirt.
It was too small.
‎格温拿去了 现在没事了
Gwen took it. It's okay now.
‎天杀的布莱恩
Frickin' Brian.
‎我尽我所能让孩子们高兴
I try to do whatever I can
to make sure my kids never feel bad,
‎可还是不小心整骚包了
but sometimes things
slip through my cracks.
‎这号码…好长
That's… That's a lot of numbers.
‎布莱恩 是我
Brian, it's me.
‎我管你现在是日本几点呢？
‎反正我在威斯康辛
What the hell do I care
what time it is in Japan?
‎我管你现在是日本几点呢？
‎反正我在威斯康辛
I'm in Wisconsin. [scoffs]
‎是啊 我…
Yeah, I…
‎你好歹给儿子寄件合身的衣服啊
You need to send your son
a shirt that actually fits.
‎他都跟你姐一样高了
He's as tall as your sister now.
‎还有 告诉你床上那娘们儿 把嘴闭上
And tell that broad in your bed
to close her mouth.
‎我能听到她打呼
I can hear her snorin'!
‎她在跟日本通电话
She's on the phone with Japan.
‎日本？
Japan?
‎再见您呐
Sayonara.
[funky rock music playing]
‎虾鱼天就得这么过
Now, this is you spend a dainy ray.
‎下雨癫
Rainy dray.
‎天
Day.
‎喂 小心
Hey, be careful.
‎在屋里开伞会倒霉的
It's bad luck to open a brella inside.
‎等等
Hold up.
‎再说一次
Say that word again.
‎伞
Brella.
‎每次下雨 妈就想不起那是啥玩意儿
Like, when it's raining, and Mom can
never remember what they're called,
‎她总说：“把你们的咦…伞拿上”
and she's always like,
"Take your, um… brella."
[both laughing]
‎不是吧
No way!
[both chuckling]
‎伞
Brella.
‎等等 他是不是很火辣？
Wait, is he hot?
Uh…
‎是呢
Yeah.
‎喂 雨停了
Hey, it stopped raining.
‎她说得对 我们出去吧
[gasps] She's right. Let's get outta here.
["No Rain" by Blind Melon playing]
♪ All I can say
Is that my life is pretty plain ♪
♪ I like watching the puddles
Gather rain ♪
♪ You know I'd like to keep
My cheeks dry today, hey ♪
♪ So stay with me and I'll have it made ♪
♪ And I don't understand
Why I sleep all day ♪
♪ And I start to complain
That there's no rain… ♪
[song fades out]
‎你们记得是怎么出来的吗？
Do you guys remember coming out here?
‎不记得
No.
‎但我很高兴我们出来了
‎今天过得很不错
But I'm glad we did.
It ended up being a pretty solid day.
‎我希望这一切永远不要结束
I hope this never ends.
‎孩子们 你们的课表来了
Kids, your school schedules came!
‎夏天终于结束了 终于可以消停了
Summer is finally over.
All this is gonna end.
[rock music playing]
‎字幕翻译：Zeo Niu